Kheel, Theodore W. Punta Cana Files. 6021/011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Re. Club Med, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Saul Kagan Letters Re. Protekair, Coddetreisa and Other Loans, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Rolando Gonzalez-Bunster, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Coddetreisa - Joint Venture Operation with Peter Streit (Development of Hotel), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Coddetreisa-Club Med Insurance, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Includes mostly Spanish language material
- Coddetreisa Newco-Club Med Lease (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Dominican Republic - Tourist Development Laws, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Includes English/Spanish and some Spanish language material
- Tax Memos and Laws, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Coddetreisa-Lizandro Castillo Contract, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Coddetreisa - Miscellany, 1969-1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Punta Cana - Proposed Agreement between Coddetreisa And East-West Financial Services, Ltd., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Coddetreisa - Stock Certificates, 1966-1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Includes almost entirely Spanish language material
- Coddetreisa - Shareholder Resolutions, 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Coddetreisa Shareholder List Notes, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Mostly handwritten material
- Coddetreisa - Copies of Stock Certificates, 1971-1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Coddetresia - Stock File - Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Coddestreisa Stockholders - Shareholder Mailings, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Gateway Sporting Goods - American Transfer Company, 1984-1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Memorandum of Understanding (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Presubscription Letter of Intent, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Prospective Purchasers - Re. Punta Cana Yacht Club, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Purchase Contracts, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Accredited Investor Statement (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Explanatory Statement (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Information Re. Lots, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Land Values, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Condominium Statutes and Bylaws (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Punta Cana - Legal Research, 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Punta Cana - Legal research Re. Purchase of Land by Foreigners (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Punta Cana Beach Resort - Investigation into Proprietary Title to Punta Cana - Dr. Lamm, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Punta Cana - New Hotel - Smith Barney and Goldman Antonetti Agreements, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Punta Cana - New Hotel - Smith Barney Investment Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Punta Cana - New Hotel - Smith Barney Engagement Letter, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Punta Cana Hotel Project - Smith Barney Cash Flow Analysis, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Smith Barney - Proposed Press Release (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Punta Cana Beach Resort - Peat Marwick Main and Company Proposal, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Dupont Plaza Hotel, San Juan, Puerto Rico - Collective Bargaining Agreement (English), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Dupont Plaza - Correspondence - Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Dupont Plaza - Collective Bargaining Agreement (Spanish), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  Almost entirely Spanish language material
- Master Stock List - Blue Certificates, 1987-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Includes some handwritten records of stock purchases
- Coddetreisa - Shareholder Information Re. Kheel Family Lists, 1986-1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes some handwritten material
- Coddetreisa Stock Book 1986, 1986-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Coddetreisa - Shareholder Information Re. General File, 1971-1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Coddetreisa - Punta Cana Beach Club, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes some handwritten records
- American Bank and Trust v. Coddetreisa, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- American Bank and Trust v. Coddetreisa - Extra Legal, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- American Bank and Trust v. Coddetreisa - Miscellany and Notes, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Incudes news clippings
- Papers Re. $95,000 Debt, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Client's Papers - Stock Transfer Case, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Papers Relating to TWK $250,000 Loan, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Punta Cana Airport Company CAE (Corporacion Aeroportuaria del Este, S.A.) - Corporacion Electricia Y De Servicios Punta Cana, S.A., 1995- 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Punta Cana Airport Company CAE - Newco's Interest in CAE, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Punta Cana Airport Company CAE - Summary of Differences on Club Med Airport Purchase, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  April 30, 1997
- Punta Cana Airport Company CAE - Information About the Airport, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Punta Cana Airport Company CAE - Negotiations with USAIR, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Punta Cana Airport Company CAE - Agreements, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Punta Cana Airport Company CAE - Financials, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- American International Underwriters - Correspondence - Re. Purchase of Lots, 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Punta Cana Shareholders' Index, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Fashion Place Associates - Stockholder Information Records, 1988-1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Memorandum of Understanding between Cornell University Biodiversity Laboratory at Punta Cana, and Natural History Museum and Biodiversity Research Center of the University of Kansas, and Centro Nacional de Control de Enfermedades Tropicales of the Secreta (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Research Agreement between E.I. duPont de Nemours and Company, Cornell University Biodiversity Laboratory and Fondacion Ecologica Punta Cana, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Memorandum of Understanding between Jardin Botanico Nacional, Department of Plant Biology of Cornell University and Bailey Hortorium Hermarium, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Memorandum of Agreement - Environment and Sustainable Food Systems, Cornell University, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Memorandum of Understanding between the Grupo Punta Cana from Dominican Republic and Cornell University, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Cornell Biodiversity Lab at Punta Cana Agreement, Including the Punta Cana Ecological Foundation, Cornell University, Grupo Punta Cana, Frank R. Rainieri, Task Foundation and Theodore W. Kheel, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Press Release - Background and Description, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Re. Kellogg Foundation, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Financials, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Cartagena Protocol on Biosafety, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Cornell Undergraduate Research Program on Biodiversity - Final Report, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  July 12- 30, 1999
- Empire State College - Punta Cana Ecological Foundation, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  April 12, 2005
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Harvard University - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Harvard Medical School, United Nations Conference on Biodiversity, Human Health and the Millennium Development Goals, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Punta Cana Institute for Virtual Enterprise - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Punta Cana Institute for Virtual Enterprise - El Programa "Con Freddy y punto", 2005 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Item is a VHS cassette; Spanish language material; May 30, 2005
- Punta Cana Institute for Virtual Enterprise - Reportajes Punta Cana, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Item is a CD; Spanish language material
- Punta Cana Institute for Virtual Enterprise - Stephen Leavenworth/Stuart Schulman Study - Environmental Protection Versus Economic Development: The Case of Punta Cana, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Punta Cana Institute for Virtual Enterprise - Stuart Schulman - Biography (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Punta Cana Institute for Virtual Enterprise - Brochures, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Punta Cana Institute for Virtual Enterprise - Notes, Research, and Miscellany, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Pace University - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  February 24, 2004
- Pikitch, Ellen - Pew Institute for Ocean Science, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Stevens Institute of Technology - Correspondence, 2003-2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Stevens Institute of Technology - Business List, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Stevens Institute of Technology - Financials, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Stevens Institute of Technology - Educational/Environmental Exploration Program, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Stevens Institute of Technology - Doctor of Engineering Diploma, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  Copies of Theodore Kheel's honorary degree from the Stevens Institute of Technology; May 27, 2004
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Stevens Institute of Technology - Brochure/Articles, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Stevens Institute of Technology - Raveche, Harold J., 2005 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - University of California at Berkeley - Correspondence, 1998-2005 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - University of Illinois - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Gifts to Universities/Research Foundations, 1999-2005 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - University of Miami - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- University of Miami - Scoping Fieldwork Report, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Punta Cana Files - Co-Evolution Institute, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  September 15, 2004
- Columbia University Medical Center - Scott M. Hammer, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Punta Cana - Center for Environmental Research and Conservation (CERC), 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Punta Cana - Wildlife Trust - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  October 22, 2002
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Columbia University CERC - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Columbia University - CERC Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 41)
- CERC - New York Biodiversity Research and Conservation Database, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Columbia University - CERC Pamphlets/Brochures, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Columbia University - CERC - New York Botanical Garden, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Michael Selzer - Business Enterprises for Sustainable Travel, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - National Audubon Society - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - National Audubon Society - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - National Aquarium of Santo Domingo - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - TWK's Apartments Leased to Institutions, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- East Point Tourist Resorts - Republica de Panama, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Marlin Point Resources, Inc. - Republica de Panama, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Punta Cana Beach Resort/ Press Release, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  August 10, 1988
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Profitability Projections, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Percentage of Ownership, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - "Regulation D" Securities Law Re. Accredited Investor (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Memorandum of Understanding (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Investor's Statement (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Fashion Place Associates and Frank Rainieri Re. Punta Cana Yacht Club Purchase, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Contract of Sale and Mortgage by Citibank (Punta Cana Yacht Club) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Punta Cana Resort and Club - Telephone List, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Golf Villas Individual Rates, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Investment Residence Program, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Punta Cana Resort and Club Upgrades Hotel Rooms and Restaurants, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Includes a CD
- Punta Cana - The Center for Environmental Leadership in Business - Glenn Prickett, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Cap Cana Project, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Yacht Club, S.A. - Proposed Acquisition of Properties (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Caribbean Clubs International - Joint Venture Proposal, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Punta Cana - Stellar Company (Lou Dobbs), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- PriceWaterhouseCoopers (Financials), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Fundacion Ecologica Punta Cana, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Grupo Punta Cana - Proposed Restructuring, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Put and Loan Agreement, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Loan Agreement between Joft and Hacienda Punta Cana, S.A., 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Re. CAE - Citibank L/T Loan - Dresdner Bank, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Invoices for Legal Services, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Club Med - Information, 1984-1999 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Punta Cana Golf Course, 1987-1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Correspondence Re. Gold Course Design, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Punta Cana Golf Course - Management Proposal to the Central Bank of the Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Golf Course Design Agreements, 1988-1994 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Punta Cana Golf Course Development Plan, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- American Society of Golf Course Architects (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Robert Trent Jones' Biography, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Punta Cana Golf Course - Notes (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Miscellany, Brochures, Etc., 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Punta Cana - Golf Course Design - Eco-Tourism, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Doral Estates and International Golf and Tennis, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Punta Cana Beach Resort - Re. Carreden Group, Inc., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Ferghana Financial Services Limited - Blair/Reynolds, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Re. Rank Hotels North America, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Re. Pratt Hotel Corporation, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Punta Cana - Re. Radisson Hotels (Jon Berger), 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Punta Cana - Re. Sheraton Hotels (Roger Titley), 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Punta Cana Beach Resort - Re. Hilton International, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Scrap Book Materials, 1957-1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Includes a color photograph; includes news clippings
- Punta Cana - New Hotel - Correspondence with Hyatt, 1987-1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Punta Cana - New Hotel - Hyatt Corporation Miscellaneous Proposed Agreements, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Punta Cana - New Hotel - Hyatt Term Sheets, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Punta Cana - Re. Proposed Airline Services (Bill Hoar), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Debt/Equity Swap with Conservation International - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Corporate Design Associates, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Includes English/Japanese material; includes many color photographs; includes an architectural print
- Punta Cana Correspondence 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Punta Cana Correspondence 1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Punta Cana Correspondence 1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Punta Cana Correspondence 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Punta Cana Stockholder Letters, 1971-1992 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  Includes mail receipts; includes some Spanish language material
- Punta Cana - Development Master Plan, 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Punta Cana Beach and Golf Resort - Description of Design - Guillermo Santoni Robles, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club - Site Maps (Box 11, Folder 22)
  Entirely maps and architectural prints
- Punta Cana - Re. William Howell - Hospitality and Club Associates, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Punta Cana Beach Club - McKinley Allsopp, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Varsity Bus - Felix Diaz/TUFARO - Milagros Mantilla, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Punta Cana in Magazines and the News, 2002-2006 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Includes news clippings; includes color photographs; includes some Spanish language material
- Punta Cana News Scrapbooks, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Includes news clippings; includes some French, Spanish, and German language material
- Tourism and Biodiversity, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Birds of Punta Cana - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Birds of Punta Cana - John James Audubon Biography, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Birds of Punta Cana - Research Report - The Birds of Haiti and San Domingo, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Birds of Punta Cana - Shipping, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Hotel Statement, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Memos, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Birds of Punta Cana - Initial Proposal for Product Production, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Rosane, David - Re. Cal Vornberger Digital Design and Imaging (Proposal for Website), 2003 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  June 23, 2003
- Book Market Map, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Guide to Bird Feeding, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- The Alliance for Employment Growth and Development (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Distance Learning Files - Association of Joint Labor Management/Education Programs - Service Plan, Objectives, Information about the Association, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Distance Learning Files - Association of Joint Labor Management/Education Programs - Magazine Articles, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Distance Learning Files - Association of Joint Labor Management/Education Programs - Bread and Roses, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Distance Learning Files - Association of Joint Labor Management/Education Programs - Newsletters and Brochures, 1999-2003 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Magazine Articles, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Punta Cana - "In Search of Fabulousness" Article, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  August 13, 2004
- Articles, 1989-2003 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Punta Cana October 1999 - Photo Album (Box 12, Folder 23)
  24 color photographs
- Grameen Foundation USA, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Punta Cana Snapshots, 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Many color photographs and photographic negatives
- Nurture New York's Nature - Programs I, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Nurture New York's Nature - Programs II, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Nurture New York's Nature - Programs III, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Nurture New York's Nature - Programs IV, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Nurture New York's Nature - Initiative Updates, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- NNYN - The Gates Project for Central Park, 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- The Carriage House Center - Book Proposals, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- World Monument Fund, 2003-2006 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Lawsuit - Litigation Materials, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Mostly Spanish language material; some Spanish language material is accompanied by an English translation
- Punta Cana Files - Pictures on CDs, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Six CDs with photographs
- Punta Cana - Conservation International - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Memorandum of Understanding between Conservation International and the Punta Cana Ecological Foundation (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Punta Cana - Conservation International - Press Release, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  April 11, 2003
- Punta Cana - Conservation International - Article, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Quarterly newsletter entitled Conservation Frontlines; Spring 2003
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Columbia University - Center for Environmental Research and Conservation (CERC) - Kheel Biography (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory - Columbia University - CERC - Edward Wilson, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Punta Cana Golf and Beach Club, 2002-2006 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  Includes some Spanish and German language material; includes black and white and color photographs; includes news clippings
- Punta Cana Golf and Beach Club II, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes black and white and color photographs; includes news clippings
- Cap Cana Real Estate (Box 13, Folder 21)
  Item is English/Spanish
- Punta Cana Golf and Beach Club III, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Punta Cana Files - Golf Package/Green Fees/Golf Lessons, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Includes color photographs; includes news clippings
- Punta Cana Resort and Club - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 24)
  Entirely color photographs
- Club Mediterranee and Compania de Desarrollo Turistico, Residencial E Industrial, S.A. (Coddetreisa) - Basic Documents, 1978- 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Coddetreisa - Authorized Capital Agreements, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Corporacion Aeroportuaria del Este (CAE) - Re. Martinair (Damage to Aircraft), 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- CAE - Chase Manhattan Bank Account (Documents), 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Corporate - New York State Real Estate Tax Exemption (with affidavit of Theodore W. Kheel), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Overseas Private Investment Corporation (OPIC) Loan Agreement, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Coddetreisa - Commitment Letter, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  September 25, 1986
- Coddetreisa - Guidelines for Application to OPIC, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Agreements, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Acquisition Agreement, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Airport Agreement, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Amendment to Acquisition Agreement, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  May 2, 1978
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Modification of Airport Agreement, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  February 18, 1980
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Additional Land Agreement, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Purchase and Guarantee Agreement, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  April 8, 1978
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Lenders' Agreement, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  April 8, 1978; includes some Spanish language material
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Affidavit - Filing Fees, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Water Agreement (Draft), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Central Bank Application, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  January 10, 1978
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med 1978 Agreements (Drafts), 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Agreements Prior to 1978, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Agreements - Agreement between Trident and Coddetreisa, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  October 16, 1987
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Agreements - Affidavit of Authority to Sign (Lender's Agreement), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Coddetreisa - Re. Club Med Agreements - Lender's Agreement Interpretation, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- American International Underwriters (AIU) Agreements with Coddetreisa - Closing Documents, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Coddetreisa - Punta Cana Yacht Club - Loan Agreement between Fashion Place Associates, Inc. and Coddetreisa, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  August 15, 1986
- Punta Cana Association, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  Includes several color photographs
- Powers of Attorney - TWK - Coddetreisa, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Coddetreisa - Corporate Resolution - Republic National Bank of Miami, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Gupte, Pranay, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  December 15, 1992; includes Pranay Gupte's business card
- Coddetreisa Shares Records, 1971-1997 (Box 14, Folder 31)